Downloaded @ subs4free.club
Yeah. Like, there it is, baby.
Welcome to California.
I can't believe I'm actually here.
Believe it, sister.
This is where it all begins.
But you're sure it's cool, right?
I can crash with you guys
at your friend's place?
He doesn't even know me.
Oh, it's cool, all right.
Seth's door is always open.
To the right kind of people.
Seth told us we should always
be on the lookout
for cool young people
who see the system for what it is, Marcie.
Five minutes with Seth, and you'll know,
escaping your parents' suburban prison
was the best thing you've ever done.
Yeah.
They were so hung up
on keeping up with the Joneses,
they lost touch with their souls.
Well, Seth knows all about souls.
You'll see.
It is said,
not all those who wander are lost.
But many are.
And once lost,
they may truly be lost forever.
Home again, home again, jiggity jig.
Lucky for us, weren't stopped by no pig.
Be it ever so crumbly,
there's no place like home.
That's some statue.
Yeah. Reminds me of my old man,
after he's had a few.
Pretty out-of-sight, isn't it?
It used to belong to some
old-time movie actor.
What matters is that it's Seth's now.
And what his is ours.
Yeah, we share and share alike.
Let's get inside already.
I really got the munchies.
Wouldn't mind a sandwich myself,
before the festivities begin.
Is there some kind of party tonight?
Wherever Seth is, there's always a party.
He's where the happening is happening, man.
Come on.
Right. I just need a minute,
to get my head together.
The reflection is just an illusion.
The greatest wisdom
is seeing through appearances.
Who are you...?
Oh.
You must be their friend,
their guide or whatever. Seth.
No. I'm afraid not.
Good. A decent guru wouldn't
be caught dead in my dad's hat.
Why do your friends follow this man?
I don't know.
I haven't even met him yet.
I suppose we're all looking for something
our parents' generation doesn't care about.
Truth, I guess.
Truth lies not at the end of the road,
but inside those who walk the road.
Right.
What did you say your name was?
I didn't.
But there are some who know me as...
the Phantom Stranger.
Well, you certainly are strange.
Nice meeting you.
I wouldn't go in there, if I were you.
You're not like them.
Not yet.
You don't know me.
You don't know anything about me.
So just buzz off.
Weirdo.
Come in. Come in already.
There you are.
We thought maybe you'd
escaped our clutches.
So, where's the much-discussed Seth?
Don't sweat it.
He'll come when the time is right.
Man likes to make an entrance.
Is that him?
What, you kidding?
That's Jonathan Lord, the actor.
Don't you watch old movies?
This house used to belong to him,
before he gave it to Seth.
Gave it to him?
Why would anyone...?
People will give you
just about everything they have.
All you have to do is let them.
I'm Seth.
Pleased to meet you, Marcie.
You know my name?
I know you.
So pure and true,
Searching for meaning
in a world all screwed up
by war, pollution,
and lies.
I was once like you.
I journeyed far and wide,
trying to find my purpose
on this little pebble in space.
Then I discovered the secret.
I found my true self,
my calling.
And what is that?
Helping other people
find their true selves.
Once that happens,
any place you are
is where you are meant to be.
Heavy.
My friends have done well,
bringing you here.
Please, stay.
The night is young.
I've never met anyone like you.
There is no one else like me, Marcie.
It's stupid.
I'm frightened of you,
and drawn to you, at the same time.
There's nothing to be frightened of.
I gave you purpose.
You give me life.
You won't have her, Seth.
You've feasted enough on these children.
They come willingly.
They do my work for me.
Not this one.
She doesn't know what you are.
Let her go. Now.
Only a true innocent can defeat me.
And we both know,
you're far from innocent.
You've infested this plane too long, Seth.
Tonight, it ends.
I don't think so.
The power of the ouroboros pendant
assures me endless time.
It's my circle of everlasting life.
Let's test that theory.
Your power is waning, dark one.
I have more than enough to finish you.
Stranger, wait.
I have great power.
I can offer you much.
Even end your wandering.
We can help each other.
I will help, evil one.
I'll end the eons of misery
you've inflicted on others.
Well done, my dear.
You're my very favorite houseguest
in centuries.
I don't understand.
What's happening?
Who is this guy?
Don't you recognize him, Marcie?
He's the Man.
He's the system.
The status quo.
Marcie, you must get away from here.
He is a blight.
No, he's good.
You're the invader here.
Seth's appearance is a lie.
Don't believe him.
Your aura is remarkable, Stranger.
You are positively brimming with life.
Unlike you, Seth.
You walk this realm in living death,
a parasite.
I'll live off you for a hundred years.
No longer will I be reduced to draining scraps
from these lost whelps.
Run, Marcie. Run.
They barely whetted my appetite.
You searched for the truth, Marcie.
What do you think of it?
It's so...
groovy.
My mind is blown, Seth.
Your power,
it's a shining, brilliant thing.
You walk in eternity.
A king of ages.
But you don't have it all.
Not yet.
Don't you know what every king needs?
A queen.
I was searching for my purpose.
My truth.
And I found it.
I found you.
Darling child.
No.
You little bitch.
I'll kill you.
Ick.
I'll have you free in a min...
I hoped you would make the right choice.
What now, Marcie?
Keep searching for your truth?
Truth lies not at the end of a road,
but inside those who walk the road.
I'll keep traveling for now.
Who knows what I'll find? But...
I'll bring my own truth with me.
How does that sound, Stra...?